export const chapter = "Chapter -11: Ekalavya ";
export const noOfActivities = 3;

if (localStorage.getItem("activityNumber") == 1) {
  activityData = {
    activity: "Tick the correct option:",
    questions: [
      [
        {
          question: "Who expresses interest in learning archery?",
          optionA: "Drona",
          optionB: "Ekalavya",
          optionC: "The tribal prince",
          correctAnswer: "Ekalavya",
        },
        {
          question:
            "Why does Drona refuse to teach the person who wants to learn archery?",
          optionA: "Lack of skill",
          optionB: "Not a prince",
          optionC: "Already has a teacher",
          correctAnswer: "Not a prince",
        },
        {
          question: "Where is Drona located?",
          optionA: "Hastinapur",
          optionB: "Tribal village",
          optionC: "Mud statue",
          correctAnswer: "Hastinapur",
        },
        {
          question: "What does the person consider as their guru?",
          optionA: "Drona",
          optionB: "Mud statue",
          optionC: "Ekalavya",
          correctAnswer: "Mud statue",
        },
        {
          question:
            "What is the reason given for Drona not teaching the tribal prince?",
          optionA: "Lack of interest",
          optionB: "Princes of Hastinapur",
          optionC: "Poor boy",
          correctAnswer: "Princes of Hastinapur",
        },
        {
          question:
            "What does Ekalavya offer as a fee to Drona for learning archery?",
          optionA: "Money",
          optionB: "His bow and arrows",
          optionC: "Thumb of his right hand",
          correctAnswer: "Thumb of his right hand",
        },
        {
          question: "How does Ekalavya consider Drona as his teacher?",
          optionA: "By attending formal classes",
          optionB: "Practicing before Drona's image",
          optionC: "By winning archery competitions",
          correctAnswer: "Practicing before Drona's image",
        },
        {
          question: "Who does Ekalavya claim is a better archer than Arjuna?",
          optionA: "Drona",
          optionB: "Himself",
          optionC: "The tribal prince",
          correctAnswer: "Himself",
        },
        {
          question:
            "What is Ekalavya's response when asked for his fee by Drona?",
          optionA: "Refuses to pay",
          optionB: "Agrees and pays with money",
          optionC: "Agrees and sacrifices his thumb",
          correctAnswer: "Agrees and sacrifices his thumb",
        },
        {
          question: "What motivates Ekalavya to become a skilled archer?",
          optionA: "To impress the princes",
          optionB: "To save the princes from danger",
          optionC: "To challenge Arjuna",
          correctAnswer: "To save the princes from danger",
        },
      ],
    ],
  };
}

if (localStorage.getItem("activityNumber") == 2) {
  activityData = {
    activity: "Fill in the blank with correct option:",
    questions: [
      [
        {
          question: "__________ expresses interest in learning archery.",
          optionA: "Drona",
          optionB: "Ekalavya",
          optionC: "The tribal prince",
          correctAnswer: "Ekalavya",
        },
        {
          question:
            "Drona refuses to teach the person who wants to learn archery because he is not a __________.",
          optionA: "Lack of skill",
          optionB: "Not a prince",
          optionC: "Already has a teacher",
          correctAnswer: "Not a prince",
        },
        {
          question: "Drona is located in __________.",
          optionA: "Hastinapur",
          optionB: "Tribal village",
          optionC: "Mud statue",
          correctAnswer: "Hastinapur",
        },
        {
          question: "The person considers the __________ as their guru.",
          optionA: "Drona",
          optionB: "Mud statue",
          optionC: "Ekalavya",
          correctAnswer: "Mud statue",
        },
        {
          question:
            "Ekalavya offers the __________ as a fee to Drona for learning archery.",
          optionA: "Money",
          optionB: "His bow and arrows",
          optionC: "Thumb of his right hand",
          correctAnswer: "Thumb of his right hand",
        },
        {
          question:
            "Ekalavya considers Drona as his teacher by practicing before __________.",
          optionA: "Attending formal classes",
          optionB: "Praying to the gods",
          optionC: "Drona's image",
          correctAnswer: "Drona's image",
        },
        {
          question: "Ekalavya claims to be a better archer than __________.",
          optionA: "Drona",
          optionB: "Himself",
          optionC: "The tribal prince",
          correctAnswer: "Himself",
        },
        {
          question:
            "Ekalavya responds to Drona's request for a fee by sacrificing __________.",
          optionA: "Money",
          optionB: "His bow and arrows",
          optionC: "His thumb of the right hand",
          correctAnswer: "His thumb of the right hand",
        },
        {
          question:
            "Ekalavya is motivated to become a skilled archer to save the princes from __________.",
          optionA: "Danger",
          optionB: "Boredom",
          optionC: "Hunger",
          correctAnswer: "Danger",
        },
        {
          question:
            "Drona refuses to teach the tribal prince because he teaches only the __________ of Hastinapur.",
          optionA: "Common people",
          optionB: "Princes",
          optionC: "Warriors",
          correctAnswer: "Princes",
        },
      ],
    ],
  };
}

if (localStorage.getItem("activityNumber") == 3) {
  activityData = {
    activity: "Write 'True' for True and 'False' for False statements:",
    questions: [
      [
        {
          question: "Drona agrees to teach the tribal prince.",
          optionA: "True",
          optionB: "False",
          correctAnswer: "False",
        },
        {
          question:
            "Ekalavya offers money as a fee to Drona for learning archery.",
          optionA: "True",
          optionB: "False",
          correctAnswer: "False",
        },
        {
          question: "The person considers Ekalavya as their guru.",
          optionA: "True",
          optionB: "False",
          correctAnswer: "False",
        },
        {
          question: "The tribal prince is already a skilled archer.",
          optionA: "True",
          optionB: "False",
          correctAnswer: "False",
        },
        {
          question: "Drona is located in a tribal village.",
          optionA: "True",
          optionB: "False",
          correctAnswer: "False",
        },
        {
          question: "Ekalavya claims to be a better archer than Drona.",
          optionA: "True",
          optionB: "False",
          correctAnswer: "False",
        },
        {
          question:
            "Ekalavya's motivation to become a skilled archer is to impress the princes.",
          optionA: "True",
          optionB: "False",
          correctAnswer: "False",
        },
        {
          question:
            "The people who initially ran away felt proud when they discovered the truth about the 'lion'.",
          optionA: "True",
          optionB: "False",
          correctAnswer: "False",
        },
        {
          question: "Drona teaches only the common people of Hastinapur.",
          optionA: "True",
          optionB: "False",
          correctAnswer: "False",
        },
        {
          question:
            "Ekalavya sacrifices his thumb willingly as a fee to Drona.",
          optionA: "True",
          optionB: "False",
          correctAnswer: "False",
        },
      ],
    ],
  };
}

export var activityData;
